Guide to the Frauke Heard-Bey and David Heard collection AD.MC.064
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Periodicals and news digests, 1972-2015
  - News digest services: Middle East Economic Survey (MEES): A Weekly Review of News and Views on Middle East Oil (Beirut / Nicosia: Middle East Petroleum and Economic Publications), 1972-2000
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 18-21, May 4 - 25 1998 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 22-26, June 1 - 29, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 27-30, July 6 - 27, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 31-35, August 3 - 31, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 36-39, September 7 - 28, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 40-43, October 5 - 26, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 44-48, November 2 - 30, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 49-52, December 7 - 28, 1998 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 1-4, January 4 - 25, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 5-8, February 1 - 22, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 9-13, March 1 - 29, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 14-17, April 5 - 26, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 18-22, May 3 - 31, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 23-26, June 7 - 28, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 27-30, July 5 - 26, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 31-35, August 2 - 30, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 36-39, September 6 - 27, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 40-43, October 4 - 25, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 44-48, November 1 - 29, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Volume XLII, Nos. 49-52, December 6 - 27, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Volume XLIII, Nos. 2-5, January 10 - 31, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Volume XLIII, Nos. 6-9, February 7 - 28, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Volume XLIII, Nos. 10-13, March 6 - 27, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Volume XLIII, No. 16, April 17, 2000 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Index to Volume XXII, October 23, 1978 - October 15, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Index to Volume XXIII, October 22, 1979 - October 13, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Index to Volume XXIV, October 20, 1980 - October 12, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Index to Volume XXV, October 19, 1981 - October 11, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Index to Volume XXVI, October 18, 1982 - October 10, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Index to Volume XXVII, October 17, 1983 - October 8, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Index to Volume XXVIII, October 15, 1984 - October 7, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Index to Volume XXIX, October 14, 1985 - October 6, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Index to Volume XXX, October 13, 1986 - October 5, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Index to Volume XXXI, October 12, 1987 - October 3, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Index to Volume XXXII, October 10, 1988 - October 2, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Index to Volume XXXIII, October 9, 1989 - October 1, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Index to Volume XXXIV, October 8, 1990 - September 30, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Index to Volume XXXV, October 7, 1991 - September 28, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Index to Volume XXXVI, October 5, 1992 - September 27, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Index to Volume XXXVII, October 4, 1993 - September 26, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Index to Volume XXXVIII, October 3, 1994 - September 25, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Press clipping services: PAVAC (Abu Dhabi), 1984-1986
    - PAVAC: Nos. 83-88, May 9-15, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 129-138, July 5 - 16, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 139-151, July 17 - 31, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 152-163, August 1 - 15, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 164-176, August 16 - 30, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 177-184, September 3 - 13, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 185-195, September 15 - 27, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 198-211, October 1 - 16, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 212-222, October 17 - 29, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 225-236, November 1 - 14, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 237-249, November 15 - 29, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 250-260, December 1 - 16, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Nos. 261-272, December 17 - 31, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 1-11, January 1 - 15, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 13-25, January 17 - 31, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 26-37, February 2 - 14, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 38-49, February 16 - 28, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 50-61, March 2 - 14, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 62-75, March 16 - 31, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 76-87, April 1 - 14, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 88-100, April 15 - 30, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 101-112, May 1 - 14, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 113-126, May 15 - 30, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 127-138, June 1 - 13, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 139-149, June 15 - 30, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 198-210, September 1 - 15, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 211-219, 120-122, September 17 - 30, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 123-135, October 1 - 15, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 136-149, October 16 - 31, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 150-162, November 2 - 16, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 163-170, 271-273, November 17 - 30, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 274-284, December 1 - 15, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 2, Nos. 285-298, December 16 - 30, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 1-13, January 2 - 16, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 14-25, January 18 - 30, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 26-36, February 1 - 12, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 37-49, February 13 - 27, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 50-63, March 1 - 16, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 64-76, March 17 - 31, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 77-89, April 1 - 16, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 90-101, April 17 - 30, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 102-114, May 1 - 15, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 115-127, May 17 - 31, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 129-137, June 2 - 15, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 138-150, June 16 - 30, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 151-164, July 1 - 16, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 165-177, July 17 - 31, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 178-186, August 2 - 12, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 187-201, August 13 - 31, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 202-212, September 1 - 15, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 214-227, September 16 - 30, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 228-237, 239-240, October 1 - 15, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 241-245, 249-253, October 16 - 30, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 254-265, November 1 - 13, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 267-280, November 16 - 30, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 282, 284-292, December 4 -15, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - PAVAC: Vol. 3, Nos. 293-304, December 16 - 30, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Press clippings: chronological, 1984-1997
    - June 1984 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - July 1984 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - August 1984 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - September 1984 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - October 1984 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - November 1984 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - December 1984 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - January 1985 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - February 1985 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - March 1985 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - April 1985 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - May 1985 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - June 1985 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - July - August 1985 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - September - October 1985 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - November 1985 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - December 1985 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - January - February 1986 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - March - May 1986 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - June - July 1986 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - August - September 1986 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - October - November 1986 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - December 1986 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - January - February 1987 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - March - April 1987 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - May 1987 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - June 1987 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - July - August 1987 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - September - October 1987 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - November - December 1987 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - January 1988 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - February - March 1988 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - April - May 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - June - July 1988 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - August - September 1988 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - October 1988 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - November - December 1988 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - January - March 1989 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - April - August 1989 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - September - December 1989 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - January 1990 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - February 1990 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - March 1990 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - April 1990 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - May 1990 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - June 1990 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - July 1990 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - August 1990 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - September 1990 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - October 1990 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - November 1990 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - December 1990 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - January 1991 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - February 1991 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - March 1991 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - April 1991 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - May 1991 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - June 1991 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - July 1991 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - August 1991 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - September 1991 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - October 1991 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - November 1991 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - December 1991 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - January 1992 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - February 1992 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - March 1992 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - April 1992 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - May 1992 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - June 1992 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - July 1992 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - August 1992 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - September 1992 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - October 1992 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - November 1992 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - December 1992 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - January 1993 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - February - June 1993 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - September - September 1993 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - January - July 1994 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - August - December 1994 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - January - June 1995 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - July - December 1995 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - January - June 1996 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - July - December 1996 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - 1997 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Press clippings: thematic, 1998-2015
    - Agriculture, 2002-2010 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Aid, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Defense, 1998-2009 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Dubai, and other emirates, 2001-2005, 2014 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Economy, 2001-2004 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Economy, 2005-2009, 2012 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Education, 2001-2014 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Government, 1999-2015 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Information (media), 2000-2005 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Labor, 1990, 2000-2005 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Law, 2000-2011 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Population statistics, 2003-2004 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Social, 1999-2004 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Social, 2005-2011 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Water and electricity, 2000-2008 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers: special editions and supplements, 1983-2011
    - Emirates News: special inserts for National Day (1997, 2002)
    - Gulf Mirror: Bahrain National Day, Dec. 1, 1983
    - Gulf News: Dubai Municipality, Gulf News Supplement, Dec. 31, 1986
    - Gulf News: Sharjah, Gulf News Supplement, Mar. 12, 1987
    - Gulf News: Bahrain Gulf News Supplement, Dec. 16, 1987
    - Gulf News: Leading Businessmen of Dubai: Part 1, Gulf News Supplement, Jun. 1, 1988
    - Gulf News: A Warm Welcome Their Royal Highnesses The Prince and Princess of Wales, Gulf News Pictorial Souvenir, Mar. 14, 1989
    - Gulf News: Manufacturing Industries, Gulf News Supplement, Mar. 30, 1989
    - Gulf News: UAE National Day, Gulf News Supplement, Dec. 1, 1989
    - Gulf News: Friday Tabloid, Dec. 5, 1989
    - Gulf News: Gulf News: UK Channel Islands Isle of Man, Gulf News Special Report, Apr. 16, 1990
    - Gulf News: Tribute: HH Sheikh Rashed Bin Saeed Al Maktoum 1910-1990, Oct. 12, 1990
    - Gulf News: ADMA-OPCO 30th Anniversary 1962-1992, Gulf News Special Report, Oct. 26, 1992
    - Gulf News: Dubai Chamber or Commerce and Industry, Gulf News Special Report, Jun. 14, 1993
    - Gulf News: Gulf News Special - 30 Years: Dream to Reality, Dec. 2001
    - Gulf News: National Day 2011: United We Succeed
    - [Al-Ittihad: special supplement on the Federal Republic of Germany, Dec. 1985]
    - [Al-Ittihad: special supplement, Eid al Juluus, 27. Aug. 1991]
    - [Al-Ittihad: special supplement, 1990, events and pictures].
    - [Al-Ittihad: special supplement: GCC Countries, Nov. 1985].
    - [Al-Ittihad: special supplement. 15th National Day, Dec. 1986].
    - Al-Ittihad: special supplement, Nov. 1986.
    - Al-Ittihad: special supplement: ADMA, accomplishments, 1962-1992.
    - Al-Ittihad: special supplement, Dec. 1989.
    - Al-Ittihad: special supplement, Dec. 1989.
    - Al-Ittihad: special supplement. 26 Years of Prosperity, Aug. 1992.
    - Khaleej Times: Dubai '83, Khaleej Times Special Report, March 31, 1983
    - Khaleej Times: Abu Dhabi '83, Khaleej Times Special Report, May 18, 1983
    - Khaleej Times: Northern Emirates, Khaleej Times Special Report, July 5, 1983
    - Khaleej Times: Qatar '83, Khaleej Times Special Report, Sept. 27, 1983
    - Khaleej Times: Bahrain '83, Khaleej Times Special Report, Nov. 11, 1983
    - Khaleej Times: Photography '85, Khaleej Times Special Report, Dec. 15, 1984
    - Khaleej Times: Abu Dhabi Chamber of Commerce and Industry, Khaleej Times Special Report, May 19, 1985
    - Khaleej Times: Dubai Municipality, Khaleej Times Special Report, Sept. 14, 1985
    - Khaleej Times: Banking and Finance, Khaleej Times Special Report, November 1985
    - Khaleej Times: Sultanate of Oman, Khaleej Times Special Report, Nov. 17, 1985
    - Khaleej Times: United Arab Emirates National Day 1985, Khaleej Times Special Report, December 1985
    - Khaleej Times: Bahrain '86, Khaleej Times Special Report, May 13, 1986
    - Khaleej Times: Abu Dhabi '86, Khaleej Times Special Report, May 25, 1986
    - Khaleej Times: Dubai '86, Khaleej Times Special Report, June 19, 1986
    - Khaleej Times: Banking and Finance, Khaleej Times Special Report, Aug. 30, 1986
    - Khaleej Times: Sultanate of Oman, Khaleej Times Special Report, Nov. 19, 1986
    - Khaleej Times: United Arab Emirates National Day, Khaleej Times Special Report, Dec. 2, 1986
    - Khaleej Times: Abu Dhabi '87, Khaleej Times Special Report, Apr. 30, 1987
    - Khaleej Times: Dubai Municipality, Khaleej Times Special Report, Sept. 30, 1987
    - Khaleej Times: Khaleej Times: UAE National Day, Khaleej Times Special Report, Dec. 2, 1987
    - Khaleej Times: Federal Republic of Germany, Khaleej Times Special Report, Dec. 31, 1987
    - Khaleej Times: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations (ADCO), 25th Anniversary, Khaleej Times Special Report, Dec. 14, 1988
    - Khaleej Times: The Khaleej Times Weekend, Mar. 17, 1989
    - Khaleej Times: Abu Dhabi, Khaleej Times Special Report, June 6, 1989
    - Khaleej Times: United Arab Emirates National Day, Khaleej Times Special Report, Dec. 2, 1989
    - Khaleej Times: One Year of United Germany, Khaleej Times Special Report, Oct. 3, 1991
  - General, 1974-2011
    - Al-'Asima = [The Capital: monthly magazine of the Municipality of Abu Dhabi], two issues, 1991-1992 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Al-Hilal (Vol. 6, Issue no. 32): Special Issue: [30 Years of Zayed's Vision], December 1991 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Al Majlis. (ADNH publication) Vol. 1, No. 1. First quarter, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Architectural Review, June 1977: United Arab Emirates (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Dubai International Airport Magazine and Duty Free Guide (20th Anniversary of the UAE), Dec. 1991 - Jan. 1992 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Emirates News: special supplement, on 31st anniversary of Sheikh Zayed's accession, August 6, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Emirates News: special supplement, National Day, [December 1997] (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Emirates News: special supplement, National Day [December 1998] (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - E+ [entertainment weekly magazine], April 1, 2010 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Gulf Business (Vol.13, No. 13), Jan. 25-Feb. 7, 2009 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Gulf Commercial & Tourist Newsletter (Vol. 1, No. 1), July 1974 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Horizons [entertainment magazine] (Galadari Publishing}, May 15, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Khaleej Times Weekend supplement [cover story on visit of Prince Charles and Princess Diana to the UAE], March 17, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Khawlah Bint Al-Azwar: Majalat Al-'Askarīyah [military magazine for women, Issue No. 1], December 1996 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Mujtama' al-Shurta [Community of Police], December 2008 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Municipalities (General Secretariat of U.A.E. Municipalities), Vol. 13, issue 150, November 1992 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Municipalities (General Secretariat of U.A.E. Municipalities), Vol. 13, issue 156, May 1993 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Municipalities (General Secretariat of U.A.E. Municipalities), Vol. 14, issue 157, June 1993 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Time Out Abu Dhabi, March 2004 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Turath [Heritage], Issue 101, January 2008 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - What's On, Issue 254 (20th Anniversary Issue), June 1999 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Zahrat al-Khaleej [Flower of the Gulf], Year 21, Issue 115, January 15, 2000 / 9 Shawwal 1420 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - 999: Society and Security Monthly, Issue 456 [separate English and Arabic issues], December 2008 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - 999: Society and Security Monthly [special National Day supplement], December 2008 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Research materials and projects
  - Materials and binders, 1964-1977
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, chronological, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: A. Statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: B. Education, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: C. Religion, 1967-1969 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: D. Education, 1969-1971 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: F. Economy, 1969-1972 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: G. Oil industry, 1970-1972 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: H.-J. Urban planning, Law, 1970-1971 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: K. Administrative structure (government), 1968-1971 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: M. Anecdotes; N. General, 1964-1971 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Binders: Abu Dhabi, topical: O. Chronology; P. Archaeology, 1965 and undated, circa 1969-1970 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Binders: Arab Report and Record (selected excerpts), 1968 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Binders: Arab Report and Record (selected excerpts), 1969 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Binders: Arab Report and Record (selected excerpts), 1970 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Binders: Arab Report and Record (selected excerpts), 1971 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Binders: Dubai; background and general, 1969-1976 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Binders: Dubai; government, 1966-1976 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Binders: Dubai; medical, and Rashid Hospital, 1973-1975 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Binders: Dubai; Reuters Bulletins (excerpts), 1971-1976 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Binders: Dubai; trade statistics, 1965-1976 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Binders: Federation, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Binders: Federation, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Binders: Federation, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Binders: Federation, 1971: January - September (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Binders: Federation, 1971: October - December (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Binders: Federation, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Binders: UAE, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Binders: UAE, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Publication projects, 1992-2012
    - Arab Integration (Georgetown University symposium and book): Paper (Frauke Heard-Bey), manuscript drafts and notes, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Arab Integration Georgetown University symposium and book): Paper (Frauke Heard-Bey), speaker's copy, April 9, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Arab Integration Georgetown University symposium and book): Paper (Frauke Heard-Bey), version submitted for publication, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Arab Integration (Georgetown University symposium and book): Papers presented (by other scholars), 1992 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Arab Integration (Georgetown University symposium and book): Program and list of participants, April 1992 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - The Gulf and Central Asia (Peter Huenseler research project): outline and selected scholarly articles, December 1999 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - The Gulf and Central Asia (Peter Huenseler research project): selected scholarly articles, December 1999 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E.,, history of: archival documents, copied (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E.,, history of: Articles copied from International Insurance Monitor (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Articles copied from The Review (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Company brochures (India), circa 2010 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Legal, translation of UAE Federal Law 6 of 2007 concerning the formation of the Insurance Commission (Clyde and Company), July 2007 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Press cuttings, local, 2010-2011 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Scholarly articles, 1998-2008, and undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Swiss Reinsurance--Reports and statistics, 2008-2011 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Takaful, articles about, 2008-2010, and undated (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Insurance in the U.A.E., history of: Text of book chapter, galley proof, "United Arab Emirates: Economic Boom and Insurance," by Frauke Heard-Bey, in Peter Borscheid and Niels Viggo Haeuter, editors, World Insurance: the Evolution of the Global Risk Network (Oxford University Press, 2012) (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Juma al Majid Center symposium (Dubai, April 1996): Abstracts of papers presented (Box 103, Folder 1)